Guide to the Virginia Barber Literary Agency Records, 1975-2003 RL.01329
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Organizations, 1975-1995, 1 box
  - Women's Media Group, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Women's Media Group, membership committee, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Women's Media Group, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Writer's Union of Canada, 1981 (Box 22)
- Agency Administrative Files, 1989-2003, 1 box
  Materials in the Administrative Files series include general agency correspondence, calendars, and materials documenting the sale of the VBLA to William Morris Agency, 2001-2003.
  - Correspondence, 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Sale of Virginia Barber Literary Agency to William Morris Agency, 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - Calendars, 1993-2000 (Box 23)
    Desk calendars for the years 1993, 1996-2000.
- Personal Materials, 1979-2003, 1 box
  Miscellaneous personal files maintained by Virginia Barber.
  - Barber, Virginia, 1980-1991 (Box 23)
  - Barber, Virginia, 1998 (Box 23)
  - Barber, Virginia, undated (Box 23)
  - Evans, Mary, 1979-1984 (Box 23)
  - Evans, Mary, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Franklin, John Hope gala, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - Indiana antiques, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Leake, P.D., 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Public relations, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Puttnam, David, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - William Morris Agency retirement party, 2003 (Box 23)
- Virago Books Materials, 1978-1991, 3 boxes
  During the early 1980s, the VBLA represented Virago Books, a UK publisher, and attempted to find partnerships and contracts for British books from Virago to be published in the United States. This series includes general correspondence, files for various Virago titles, and materials from some of Virago's partnerships with other publishers such as Viking or Dial Press.
  Virago titles are arranged alphabetically by book title; partnerships with other publishers are arranged chronologically; and general correspondence is included at the end of the series.
  - A Revolutionary Woman, by Sheila Fugard, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - A Star is Torn, by R. Archer and D. Simmonds, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - A Woman, by Sibilla Aleramo, 1978-1981 (Box 23)
  - A Woman's Touch, by I. Anscombe, 1980-1985 (Box 23)
  - Adorned in Dreams, by E. Wilson, 1985-1988 (Box 23)
  - Apple in the Dark, by Clarice Lispector, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Beatrice Webb Diaries, 1980-1984 (Box 23)
  - Bombers and Mash, by Raines Mins, 1981 (Box 23)
  - Close Company, by C. Park and C. Heaton, 1987-1989 (Box 23)
  - Collected Poems and Prose of Charlotte Mew, 1981-1982 (Box 23)
  - Deborah, by Esther Kreitman, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Diaries of Hannah Cullwick, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Dreams and Dilemmas, by S. Rowbotham, 1983-1988 (Box 23)
  - Eternity's Sunrise, by Marion Milner, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Ever Yours, Florence Nightingale, ed. by M. Vicinus and B. Nergaard, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Every Move You Make, by Alison Fell, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Fathers: Reflections by Daughters, ed. By Ursula Owen, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
  - Going a Governessing, by Kathryn Hughes, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Hannie Richards, by Hilary Bailey, 1984-1987 (Box 24)
  - Heart of the Race, by B. Bryan et al., 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Higher, Faster, Further, by Adrienne Blue, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - In Our Grandmother's Footsteps, by J. Clarke and J. Parkin, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Innocent Flowers: Women in Edwardian Theater, by Julia Holledge, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Is the Future Female?, by Lynne Segal, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Kissing the Rod: Anthology of 17th Century Verse, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Ladies' Screen Companion, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Landscape for a Good Woman, by Carolyn Steedman, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Letters of Katherine Mansfield and John Middleton Murray, ed. by Cherry Hankin, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Mulberry Tree, by E. Bowen, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Naming the Waves, ed. by Christian McEwen, 1989 (Box 24)
  - No Mate for the Magpie, by Frances Molloy, 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - Offside, by Gisela Elsner, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Pre-Raphaelite Women Artists by Jan Marsh and Pamela Nunn, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Semi-attached Couple and Semi-detached House, by Emily Eden, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Ship of Widows, by I. Grekova, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Sweet Desserts, by Lucy Ellmann, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Tea and Tranquillizers, by Diane Harpwood, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Testament of a Generation, by Vera Brittain, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - That Long Silence, by Shashi Deshpande, 1988 (Box 24)
  - The Bad Fox, by Alison Fell, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - The Holiday, etc., by Stevie Smith, 1981-1986 (Box 24)
  - The Men's Room, by Ann Oakley, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - The Other Bloomsbury, by V.L. Smyers and G. Hanscombe, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
  - The Sleeping Beauty, by E. Taylor, 1983 (Box 24)
  - The Tiger's Milk, by F. MacIntosh and A. Angel, 1986 (Box 24)
  - The Upstair's People, by Jennifer Dawson, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - The Virago Book of Ghost Stories, ed. by R. Dalby, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Tickle my Fancy, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
  - Truth, Dare, or Promise, ed. by Liz Heron, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Wave me Goodbye, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Wayward Girls and Wicked Women, by Angela Carter, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Wigan Pier Revisited, by Beatrix Campbell, 1984 (Box 24)
  - Union Street, by Pat Barker, 1982-1984 (Box 24)
  - Virtue of Necessity, by Elaine Hobby, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Winter in the Morning, by Janina Bauman, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Women in Society, 1981 (Box 24)
  - You Can't Get Lost in Cape Town, by Zoe Wicomb, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Women Under the Influence, by B. McConville, 1983-1985 (Box 24)
  - Women Writing About Men, by Jane Miller, 1983 (Box 24)
  - Writing Lives, ed. by Mary Chamberlain, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous titles (Box 24)
  - Virago-Beacon contract negotiations, 1984-1987 (Box 24)
  - Beacon/Virago Travelllers Series, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Virago Pioneers series, with Pantheon, 1982-1988 (Box 24)
  - Dial Press/Virago Modern Classics, 1979-1986, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Viking/Virago Modern Classics, 1984-1989, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Viking/Virago contract correspondence, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Viking/Virago press releases and publicity, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Viking/Virago partnership, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Virago Non-fiction Classics Series, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Virago upstarts, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - Sales information, 1985 and undated (Box 24)
  - Virago submissions, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Information on titles, 1984-1989 (Box 24)
  - Callil, Carmen, U.S. trip, 1978-1985 (Box 24)
  - Films, 1983 (Box 25)
  - General correspondence, 1977-1991, 9 folders (Box 25)
- Legal and Financial Materials, 1968-2003, 8 boxes
  The Legal and Financial Materials series contains files kept by the Virginia Barber Literary Agency for each of its clients as well as papers relating to other literary agents and publishers. Most files include contracts with clients, outside publishers, and film studios in draft and final states. Files also include receipts for payments, royalty statements, and tax records.
  This series has been divided into Restricted and Open Files based on the status of VBLA's clients. The files of clients who are deceased as of 2013 are open and available for researchers. Most of the series, however, falls into the Restricted Files subseries, and are closed for the lifespan of the client.
  - Restricted Files
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Legal and financial materials for living clients are closed for the life of the client. Researchers must obtain written permission from the client in order to access these materials.
    - General VBLA legal/financial papers, 1984-1998 (Box 26)
    - Abbott, Dorothy, 1987-1990 (Box 26)
    - Ackerman, Diane, 2000-2002 (Box 26)
    - Allport, Susan, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Attanasio, A. A., 1985 (Box 26)
    - Avery, Martha, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
    - Bacon, Charlotte, 2001 (Box 26)
    - Barker, Pat, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Barsocchini, Peter, 1980-2002, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Bauer, Douglas, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Benderly, Beryl, 1983-1986 (Box 26)
    - Beranbaum, Rose, 1984-1986 (Box 26)
    - Blakeslee, Sandra, 1987-2001, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Brady, Kathleen, 1990 (Box 26)
    - Brandon, Jay, 1985-1994 (Box 26)
    - Brenner, Leslie, undated (Box 26)
    - Brenton, Myron, 1975-1983 (Box 26)
    - Brown, Alan, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Brown, Michael, 1980-1986 (Box 26)
    - Brown, Rosellen, 1987-2002 (Box 26)
    - Burke, Martyn, 1992 (Box 26)
    - Byham, William, 1990-2002 (Box 26)
    - Byrd, Max, 1988-2000 (Box 26)
    - Carola, Robert, and Joseph Rechtschaffen, 1979-1986 (Box 26)
    - Carynnyk, Marco, 1973-1984 (Box 26)
    - Carynnyk, Marco, and Marta Horban, 1977-1982 (Box 26)
    - Case, Peggy, 1984-1986 (Box 26)
    - Chabon, Michael, 1990 (Box 26)
    - Chamberlain, Diane, 1994-2003 (Box 26)
    - Chertow, Marian, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Clancy, John, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Cochrane, Mick, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Cody, Joe, Patti Hagan, and George Colbert, 1979-1983 (Box 27)
    - Cohen, Judith Beth, 1978-1985 (Box 27)
    - Cohn, Rachel, 2002-2003 (Box 27)
    - Cole, K. C., 1997-2003 (Box 27)
    - Coleman, Smith and Claypool, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Conrad, Roberta, 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - Coram, Robert, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Coughlan, William, 1970-1979 (Box 27)
    - Count, Ellen, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
    - Coyle, Beverly, 1993-2000 (Box 27)
    - Cravens, Gwyneth, 1980-1986 (Box 27)
    - Cronin Jr., Edward, 1975-1985 (Box 27)
    - DeChristofero, Ron, 1978-1982 (Box 27)
    - Delbanco, Andrew, 1997-2002 (Box 27)
    - Dew, Robb Forman, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Diggett, Charles, and William Mulligan, 1980-1984 (Box 27)
    - Dodson, James, 1981-2003 (Box 27)
    - Dooley, Susan, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
    - Druett, Joan, 1987 (Box 27)
    - Dunbar, Maureen, 1986 (Box 27)
    - Eady, Toby, Agency, 1989-1990 (Box 27)
    - Eckhardt, Celia Morris, 1975-1980 (Box 27)
    - Egan, Jennifer, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Ehrlich, Paul and Anne, 1980-2003 (Box 27)
    - Ehrlich, Paul and Anne, and Loy Bilderback, 1980 (Box 27)
    - Ehrlich, Paul, and Robert Ornstein, 1986 (Box 27)
    - Eichler, Mim, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Engel, Charlotte, 1990-1992 (Box 27)
    - Fairbairns, Zoe, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Flaste, Richard, and John Noble Wilford, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
    - Fleming, Jennifer Baker, 1975-1979 (Box 27)
    - Fleming, Jennifer Baker, and Carolyn Washburne, 1975-1981 (Box 27)
    - Forche, Carolyn, 1981-2003 (Box 27)
    - Forward, Susan, 1999-2002 (Box 27)
    - Frank, Katherine, 1982-2002 (Box 27)
    - Friedman, Phillip, and Michael Tanzer, 1975-1977 (Box 27)
    - Furie, Kenneth, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Gadd, Laurence and Irna, 1982-1985 (Box 27)
    - Galinsky, Ellen, 1980-1988 (Box 27)
    - Galland, China, 1982 (Box 27)
    - Garner, Helen, 1980-1986 (Box 27)
    - Gault, John, 1976-1982 (Box 27)
    - Gee, Sue, 1991 (Box 27)
    - Geyer, Nancy, 1986-1991 (Box 27)
    - Gillespie, Larrian, 1987-1994 (Box 27)
    - Gingher, Marianne, 1982-1990 (Box 27)
    - Goodwin, Michael, 1982-1990 (Box 27)
    - Grant, Linda, undated (Box 27)
    - Gustaitis, Rasa, and Ernle Young, 1986 (Box 27)
    - Guy, David, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Hardy, Jeanne, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Havazelet, Ehud, 2000-2003 (Box 28)
    - Haviland, David, 1982 (Box 28)
    - Hegarty, Frances, 1989-1990 (Box 28)
    - Heineman, Helen, 1977-1979 (Box 28)
    - Henderson, William, 1984-1987 (Box 28)
    - van Herk, Aritha, 1983-1987 (Box 28)
    - von Herzen, Lane, 1993-1994 (Box 28)
    - Heyn, Dalma, 1991-1992 (Box 28)
    - Hill, Rebecca, 1983-1986 (Box 28)
    - Hoberman, James, and Jonathan Rosenbaum, 1979-1985 (Box 28)
    - von Hoffman, Nicholas, 1980-1992 (Box 28)
    - Hogrefe, Jeffrey, 1983-1985 (Box 28)
    - Hoover, Thomas, 1981-1988 (Box 28)
    - Hope, Karol, and Nancy Young, 1977-1982 (Box 28)
    - Huddle, David, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Hummer, Terry, 1991 (Box 28)
    - Imperato, Pascal (Pat), 1977-1985 (Box 28)
    - Imperato, Pascal (Pat), and Gregg Mitchell, 1979-1985 (Box 28)
    - Janus, Samuel, Barbara Bess, and Carol Saltus, 1976-1983 (Box 28)
    - Juska, Jane, 2002-2003 (Box 28)
    - Kagan, Elaine, 2000-2001 (Box 28)
    - Kalmus, Yvonne, 1976-1984 (Box 28)
    - Kalpakian, Laura, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Kamen, Robert, 1979-1982 (Box 28)
    - Kaufman, Wallace, 1977-1984 (Box 28)
    - Keane, John, 1977-1985 (Box 28)
    - Kidd, Lucy Armstrong, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Kidd, Sue Monk, 1987-2003 (Box 28)
    - Kiernan, Frances, 1990-2001 (Box 28)
    - Kinsolving, Katharine, undated (Box 28)
    - Kittredge, William, and Steven Krauzer, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Kole, Janet, 1975 (Box 28)
    - Landau, David, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Lapautre, Michelle, Agency, 1983-1985 (Box 28)
    - Larsen, Karen, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Lee, Susan, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Leimbach, Marti, 1989-1992 (Box 28)
    - Lentricchia, Melissa, 1988-1993 (Box 28)
    - Le Vernoy, Alec, 1998 (Box 28)
    - Levangie, Gigi, 1999-2000 (Box 28)
    - Levant, Ronald, 1986-1999 (Box 28)
    - Levine, Ann, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
    - Levine, Faye, 1985-1989 (Box 28)
    - Lieber, James, 1981-1999 (Box 28)
    - Liepman Agency, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Lingeman, Richard, 1994-2002 (Box 28)
    - Linthwaite, Illona, 1996-1999 (Box 28)
    - Lipman, Elinor, 1995-2003 (Box 29)
    - Lipsky, David, 1991-1999 (Box 29)
    - Lipsyte, Robert, 2000-2003, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Litvinov, Ivy, 1997-1999 (Box 29)
    - Louie, Elaine, 1980-1999 (Box 29)
    - Louie, Elaine, and Edward Addeo, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Lucas, Michele, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Luxenberg, Stan, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Lynch, Sarah-Kate, 2002 (Box 29)
    - Mallon, Thomas, General, 1985-1999 (Box 29)
    - Mallon, Thomas, Standing Firm, 1993-1999 (Box 29)
    - Marsh, Jan, 1986-1999 (Box 29)
    - Martin, William, and Calvin Skaggs, 1995 (Box 29)
    - Mason, Alexander, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Mason, Anita, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Matison, James and Russ Mack, 1980 (Box 29)
    - Mayle, Peter, General, 1980-89 (Box 29)
    - Mayle, Peter, General, 1990-99, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Mayle, Peter, General, 2000-2004, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Mayle, Peter, BBC - A Year in Provence and Toujours Provence (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Peter, Printing and bestseller information (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Peter, Anything Considered film, SCFV Pictures, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Peter, Movie miscellaneous, 1983-1992, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Peter, Play contract Patrick Gamble, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Peter and Ernest Chapman, 1985-1986 (Box 30)
    - Mayle, Simon, 1993 (Box 30)
    - McNeil, Helen, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Mickle, Shelley Fraser, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Mitchell, David and Cathy, and Richard Ofshe, 1979-1984 (Box 30)
    - Mitchell, Greg, 1984 (Box 30)
    - Monaco, James, 1979-1984 (Box 30)
    - Mulligan, Bill, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Murray, Yxta Maya, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Myers, Norman, 1985-1990 (Box 30)
    - Nasaw, David, 2000-2004 (Box 30)
    - Nowak, Marion, 1980 (Box 30)
    - Olsen, Sondra, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Ornstein, Robert, 1985-1989 (Box 30)
    - Ouellette, William, 1975-1978 (Box 30)
    - Ouellette, William, and Barbara Jones, 1976-1983 (Box 30)
    - Pan, Lynn, 1987-1988 (Box 30)
    - Phillips, B. J., 1975-1976 (Box 30)
    - Pizzey, Erin, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
    - Plumb, Catherine, 1976-1977 (Box 30)
    - Pope, Lois, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Powledge, Fred, 1985 (Box 30)
    - Redd, Joanne, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
    - Rickhoff, Jean, 1977-1982 (Box 30)
    - Robbins, Tom, 1977-1990 (Box 30)
    - Robertson, Mary Elsie, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Robson, Lucia St. Clair, 1984-2003 (Box 30)
    - Rose, Frank, 1980-1989 (Box 30)
    - Rosenbaum, Jonathan, 1982-1983 (Box 30)
    - Rosenberg, John, 1977-1980 (Box 31)
    - Rudner, Ruth, 1970-1984 (Box 31)
    - Russell, Franklin, 1980-1984 (Box 31)
    - Scarr, Sandra, 1982-1988 (Box 31)
    - Schaeffer, Neil, 1990-2000 (Box 31)
    - Schraffenberger, Nancy, 1973-1985 (Box 31)
    - Schultz, Vicki, 2001-2002 (Box 31)
    - Schwartz, Lynne Sharon, 1980-1997, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Sebag-Montefiore, Hugh, undated (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, General, 1983-2003, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Eden Close, 1989-1999 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Fortune's Rocks, 1998-2000 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Pilot's Wife, 1996-2001 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Resistance, 1985-2000 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Strange Fits of Passion, 1991-2000 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Weight of Water, 1996-2000 (Box 31)
    - Shreve, Anita, Where or When, 1992-2000 (Box 32)
    - Shreve, Anita, Harcourt Brace and Co., 1991-2000 (Box 32)
    - Shreve, Anita, and Lawrence Balter, 1984-2000, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, General, 1985-2003, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Payments analyses for Kings Oak, Outer Banks, Colony, 1991-1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Up Island, 1997-1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Colony Norman Twain Productions, 1993-1995 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Colony royalty statements, 1991-1997 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Low Country Citadel Entertainment, 1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Harper Collins, 1992-2000 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Downtown and Colony contracts, 1990-1996 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Downtown royalties, 1993-1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Harper Collines Colony contracts, 1991-1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Hilltowns royalties, 1993-1999 (Box 32)
    - Siddons, Anne Rivers, Harper Collins foreign rights sales, 1993-2000 (Box 32)
    - Sjostrom, Lisa, and Kathryn Geismar, 1995-1997 (Box 33)
    - Skaggs, Calvin, 1977-1999 (Box 33)
    - Sleeper, Jim, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Smith, Deborah, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Smith, Dinitia, 1985-1994 (Box 33)
    - Sparkman, Brandon, and Jane Saul, 1976-1985 (Box 33)
    - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1984-1993 (Box 33)
    - Stallings, Penny, 1983-1985 (Box 33)
    - Stanley, Autumn, 1984-1995 (Box 33)
    - Steinberg, Laurence, 1987-2002 (Box 33)
    - Stone, Elizabeth, 1978-1983 (Box 33)
    - Swan, Mary, 2001-2003 (Box 33)
    - Tanzer, Michael, 1974 (Box 33)
    - Taylor, Barbara, 1992-1997 (Box 33)
    - Taylor, John, 1997-2000 (Box 33)
    - Thomas, Lynn, 1978-1985 (Box 33)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1992-2000 (Box 33)
    - Thompson, Richard, 1984 (Box 33)
    - Tine, Robert, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Tippins, Elizabeth, 1996-2000 (Box 33)
    - Tobar, Hektor, 1997-1999 (Box 33)
    - Trott, Susan, undated (Box 33)
    - Tseo, George, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Tsiaras, Alexander, 2000 (Box 33)
    - Tyler, Sandra, 1991-2000 (Box 33)
    - Ungar, Rick, 1997 (Box 33)
    - Vargas, Alberto and Reid Austin, 1984-1995 (Box 33)
    - Verghese, Abraham, 1992-1999, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Vilmure, Daniel, 1994-1999 (Box 33)
    - Virago Press and Beacon Press, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
    - Vo, Thao Dinh, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Wales, Michael, 1984 (Box 33)
    - White, Suzanne, 2001-2002 (Box 33)
    - Wicomb, Zoe, 1995 (Box 33)
    - Wiebe, Rudy, 1978-1985 (Box 33)
    - Wiesenfeld, Cheryl, 1975-1985 (Box 33)
    - Wilford, John Noble, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Willey, Margaret, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
    - Wilson, Elizabeth, 1995 (Box 33)
    - Wohl, Lisa, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - Wolk, Michael, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Wright, Daphne, 1986-1988 (Box 33)
    - Wyler, Susan, 1980 (Box 33)
    - Xinxin, Zhang, 1986-1987 (Box 33)
    - Young, Jeffrey, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Young, Nancy, 1978-1982 (Box 33)
  - Open Files
    - Aleramo, Sibilla, 1990 (Box 34)
    - Benn, June Wedgwood, 1985-1990 (Box 34)
    - Bingham, Robert, 1997 (Box 34)
    - Bowling, Harry, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Bregman, Alice, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Brittain, Vera, 1989-1998 (Box 34)
    - Carter, Angela, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Doty, Carolyn, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Findley, Timothy, 1987-1994 (Box 34)
    - Hall, Oakley, 2000-2003 (Box 34)
    - Harris, MacDonald, 1983-1993 (Box 34)
    - Hayes, Elliott, 1982-1985 (Box 34)
    - Houying, Dai, 1984-1987 (Box 34)
    - Kohn, Barry, and Alice Matusow, 1978-1984 (Box 34)
    - Krauzer, Steven, 1982-1992 (Box 34)
    - Levine, Norman, 1979-1980 (Box 34)
    - Lewinsky, Jorge, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Lucas, Russell, 1991-1999 (Box 34)
    - Miller, Casey, and Kate Swift, 1984-1987 (Box 34)
    - Reit, Seymour, 1981-1987 (Box 34)
    - Schaeffer, Susan, 1987-1999, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Shields, Carol, 1979-1983 (Box 34)
    - Sinclair, May, 1997-1999 (Box 34)
    - Skaggs, Merrill, 1973-1983 (Box 34)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth, 1997-1999 (Box 34)
    - Throckmorton, Peter, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Wald, Carol, 1975-1985 (Box 34)
    - Waller, Leslie, 1986-1988 (Box 34)
    - Wright, L. R. (Bunny), 1985-2002 (Box 34)